Hung Hao Hsu

eMail: oscar86hsu@gmail.com

Mobile: +886-981049372

Website: https://oscarhsu.me

Profile

I always have passion about new technologies. Whether it's Cloud Computing, Artificial Intelligence, or Internet Security. Since I was 10, I will sit at the computer science area of the book store and read books about programming, internet, computer system etc.. I enjoy learning and exploring things that make our life more efficient. In the field of cloud services, I have 3 years of hands-on experience on AWS, and worked as a Cloud Engineer for 2 years.

Skills

Tools: Docker, Kubernetes, Github

Knowledge: AWS, Distributed Systems

System: Linux, Unix, Mac OS X, MySQL

Programming Language: Python, C/C++, PHP,

HTML/CSS, JavaScript

Certification

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate

AWS Certified Developer – Associate

AWS Certified Sysops Administrator – Associate

Experience

Cloud Development Engineer at eCloudvalley Digital Technology

Dec 2018 - March 2020

- Built an application that scans for potential security risks, suggestion of high availability on AWS and generated a report that highlight the issues with python.
- Designed loose coupled applications, built microservices and serverless architecture on AWS that saved around 60% of the operation cost.
- Collaborated with product team to develop code, design system and test solutions for our Cloud Management Platform.

Cloud Support Engineer at eCloudvalley Digital Technology

July 2018 - Dec 2018

- Analyzed needs of customers and provide possible solutions, supported customers with technical issues such as scaling their databases automatically and load balancing traffic for their websites.
- Established operating procedure and technical document, which drops the training time of new colleges significantly.

Project Owner at Racetrack Cloud Services

February 2019 - May 2019

- Identified client's needs and effectively communicated project scope, schedule, and budget, then planned, organize, and implement all aspects of the construction project.
- Built a prototype child toy that can analyze children's behavior while they are playing, and identify possible learning disability at an early age, such as Visual Spatial Perceptual Disorder, Developmental Dyslexia or Specific Learning Disabilities in Mathematics.
- Documented deployment and post deployment procedures.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science. National Chiao Tung University, Taiwan.

Comprehensive English Program. New York University, New York.